<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>btrfs on The Duck Channel´s Site</title>
    <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/tags/btrfs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in btrfs on The Duck Channel´s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theduckchannel.github.io/tags/btrfs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux with btrfs and KDE Plasma</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/09/02/arch-linux-with-btrfs-and-kde-plasma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/09/02/arch-linux-with-btrfs-and-kde-plasma/</guid>
      <description>Video Greetings Links Steps  Pre-Install  Update the system clock Partitioning Formatting Mounting Install Base System   Configure the system  Generate fstab Chroot Time zone Localization Network Configuration mkinitcpio Install grub   [$ grub-install &amp;ndash;target=x86_64-efi &amp;ndash;efi-directory=/boot/efi ](#&amp;ndash;grub-install&amp;mdash;targetx86_64-efi&amp;mdash;efi-directorybootefi-)  Root Password Exit, umount and reboot Create New User   Install Xorg Install KDE Plasma Enable AUR Install and Config Snapper   limits for timeline cleanup 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Zorin OS 16 with Btrfs &#43; Timeshift</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/28/install-zorin-os-16-with-btrfs-&#43;-timeshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/28/install-zorin-os-16-with-btrfs-&#43;-timeshift/</guid>
      <description>Video Greetings Links Steps  Hack Ubiquity  Install vim Editing files   Partitioning Install Update and Upgrade Install Timeshift First Snapshot    Video   Greetings Zorin OS 16 Full Install with btrfs + Timeshift
Hi all, in this video i will show how to install Zorin OS 16 with btrfs + Timeshift + grub-btrfs.
btrfs is a modern copy on write (CoW) filesystem for Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Ubuntu 21.04 with btrfs &#43; snapper &#43; grub-btrfs</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/24/install-ubuntu-21.04-with-btrfs-&#43;-snapper-&#43;-grub-btrfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/24/install-ubuntu-21.04-with-btrfs-&#43;-snapper-&#43;-grub-btrfs/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Video Greetings Links Steps  1. Install Ubuntu  Start the Ubiquitu Install Partitioning   2. Update and Upgrade 3. Install grub-btrfs 4. Snapper 5. Subvolume for Snapshots 6. Start the Services 7. Create your First Snapshot   Finish  Video   Greetings Hi all, in this video i will show how to Install Ubuntu 21.04 with btrfs filesystem, snapper and grub-btrfs.
 You need have ssd, if you use mechanical hdd, please install ext4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Linux Mint 20.2 with Btrfs [2021]</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/15082021/how-to-install-linux-mint-20.2-with-btrfs-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/15082021/how-to-install-linux-mint-20.2-with-btrfs-2021/</guid>
      <description>Links  Linux Mint Download Btrfs grub-btrfs Github  0. Intro Hi all, in this video i show how to install Linux Mint 20.2 with btrfs, snapshots and grub-btrfs.
 The boot mode will be efi; I’m assuming you already have the latest usb stick with the Linux Mint ISO.  I hope you enjoy!
1. Bios Considerations  Reset BIOS to factory default and reboot. Disable fastboot and secure boot in BIOS settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux Btrfs Kde Plasma Full Install [2021]</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/13082021/arch-linux-btrfs-kde-plasma-full-install-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/13082021/arch-linux-btrfs-kde-plasma-full-install-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, in this video i will show how to full install Arch Linux with BTRFS filesystem.
 The boot mode will be EFI. I’m assuming you already have the usb stick with the Arch Linux ISO. My internet is wired, so if you have wireless network, please go to the website that is in the description of this video and see the link to properly configure your network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manjaro with Btrfs and snapper [2021]</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/13082021/manjaro-with-btrfs-and-snapper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/13082021/manjaro-with-btrfs-and-snapper-2021/</guid>
      <description>#Links
 Manjaro Btrfs  0. Intro Hi all, in this video i show how to install Manjaro with btrfs, snapshots and Grub-Btrfs.
 The boot mode will be efi; I’m assuming you already have the usb stick with the Manjaro Linux ISO. Buggie will be Desktop Environment in this case.  I hope you enjoy!
1. Install [Subtitle 01] Any moment you can access the site in description and see every command i gave here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
