<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Duck Channel´s Site</title>
    <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Duck Channel´s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux with btrfs and KDE Plasma</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/09/02/arch-linux-with-btrfs-and-kde-plasma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/09/02/arch-linux-with-btrfs-and-kde-plasma/</guid>
      <description>Video   Greetings Arch_Linux_Install_Kde_Plasma_btrfs
Hi all, in this video i will show how to install Arch Linux with KDE Plasma and btrfs.
KDE is a software project currently comprising a desktop environment known as Plasma, a collection of libraries and frameworks (KDE Frameworks) and several applications (KDE Applications) as well.
btrfs is a modern copy on write (CoW) filesystem for Linux.
I hope you enjoy!
Links  Arch Linux - Download btrfs - ArchWiki Timeshift  Steps Pre-Install Update the system clock $ timedatectl set-ntp truePartitioning We will create as following partition scheme:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Zorin OS 16 with Btrfs &#43; Timeshift</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/28/install-zorin-os-16-with-btrfs-&#43;-timeshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/28/install-zorin-os-16-with-btrfs-&#43;-timeshift/</guid>
      <description>Video Greetings Links Steps  Hack Ubiquity  Install vim Editing files   Partitioning Install Update and Upgrade Install Timeshift First Snapshot    Video   Greetings Zorin OS 16 Full Install with btrfs + Timeshift
Hi all, in this video i will show how to install Zorin OS 16 with btrfs + Timeshift + grub-btrfs.
btrfs is a modern copy on write (CoW) filesystem for Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Install bspwm on Ubuntu 21.04</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/26/full-install-bspwm-on-ubuntu-21.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/26/full-install-bspwm-on-ubuntu-21.04/</guid>
      <description>Video Greetings Links Steps  1. Install git 2. Install bspwm 3. Finish    Video   Greetings Ubuntu 21.04 Full Install bspwm Environment
Hi all, in this video i will show how to Install a full bspwm environment on Ubuntu 21.04.
bspwm is a tiling window manager that represents windows as the leaves of a full binary tree. bspwm supports multiple monitors and is configured and controlled through messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Webmin on Ubuntu 21.04</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/25/how-to-install-webmin-on-ubuntu-21.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/25/how-to-install-webmin-on-ubuntu-21.04/</guid>
      <description>Video Greetings Links Steps  1. Update and Upgrade 2. Install Dependencies 3. Install Webmin 4. Finish    Video   Greetings Hi all, in this video i will show how to Install Webmin on Ubuntu 21.04.
Webmin is a web-based interface for system administration for Unix. Using any modern web browser, you can setup user accounts, Apache, DNS, file sharing and much more. Webmin removes the need to manually edit Unix configuration files like /etc/passwd, and lets you manage a system from the console or remotely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Ubuntu 21.04 with btrfs &#43; snapper &#43; grub-btrfs</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/24/install-ubuntu-21.04-with-btrfs-&#43;-snapper-&#43;-grub-btrfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/24/install-ubuntu-21.04-with-btrfs-&#43;-snapper-&#43;-grub-btrfs/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Video Greetings Links Steps  1. Install Ubuntu  Start the Ubiquitu Install Partitioning   2. Update and Upgrade 3. Install grub-btrfs 4. Snapper 5. Subvolume for Snapshots 6. Start the Services 7. Create your First Snapshot   Finish  Video   Greetings Hi all, in this video i will show how to Install Ubuntu 21.04 with btrfs filesystem, snapper and grub-btrfs.
 You need have ssd, if you use mechanical hdd, please install ext4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Enable Chaotic-AUR on Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/23/how-to-enable-chaotic-aur-on-arch-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/23/how-to-enable-chaotic-aur-on-arch-linux/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Video Greetings Links Steps  1. Install the Keys 2. Update and Upgrade   Finish  Video   Greetings Hi all, in this video i will show how to enable Chaotic-AUR on Arch Linux.
Chaotic-AUR is a unofficial user reposity for Arch Linux that has prebuilt binaries from the AUR.
Several apps and custom kernels are available in this repo, and this includes kernels specially tuned for gamer and desktop use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Linux Mint 20.2 Dual Boot with Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/21/how-to-install-linux-mint-20.2-dual-boot-with-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/21/how-to-install-linux-mint-20.2-dual-boot-with-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Links 1. Bios Considerations 2. Prepare Windows 3. Install Linux Mint 4. Update and Upgrade 5. Finish  Hi all, in this video i will show how to full install Linux Mint 20.2 Dual Boot with Windows 10.
 The boot mode will be EFI. I’m assuming you already have the usb stick with the Linux Mint ISO.  I hope you enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install tkg Gamer Kernel to Speed Booster on Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/21/install-tkg-gamer-kernel-to-speed-booster-on-arch-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/21/install-tkg-gamer-kernel-to-speed-booster-on-arch-linux/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Video Greetings Links Steps  1. Chaotic-AUR 2. Enable Chaotic-AUR 3. Install TKG Kernel 4. Customize Grub   Finish  Video   Greetings Hi all, in this video i will show how to install TKG Gamer Kernel on Arch Linux.
You only need have one system with Arch Linux fully installed.
I hope you enjoy!
Links  Arch Linux Arch Linux Wiki Arch Linux Wiki - Kernel Chaotic-AUR  Steps 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux Full Install with bspwm</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/20/arch-linux-full-install-with-bspwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/20/arch-linux-full-install-with-bspwm/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, in this video i will show how to full install Arch Linux with bspwm desktop environment.
 The boot mode will be EFI. I’m assuming you already have the usb stick with the Arch Linux ISO. If you use wireless network, please go to the site in the description and see the link to properly configure your network.  I hope you enjoy!
Links  Download the latest Arch Linux ISO Connect to the Internet - Arch Linux Wiki Yay Arch Linux Wiki - Swap File Duck Channel´s bspwm-install  1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install LAMP Server on Arch Linux (Apache&#43;PHP&#43;MariaDB) [2021]</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/17082021/how-to-install-lamp-server-on-arch-linux-apache&#43;php&#43;mariadb-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/17082021/how-to-install-lamp-server-on-arch-linux-apache&#43;php&#43;mariadb-2021/</guid>
      <description>Links  Arch Linux Apache MariaDB PHP  0. Intro Hi all, in this video i will show how to install LAMP Server on Arch Linux.
I hope you enjoy!
1. Install Apache $ sudo pacman -S apacheSave an close the file.
$ sudo systemctl enable --now httpd$ sudo systemctl status httpdEdit /srv/http/index.html and put following lines:
&amp;lt;html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Welcome&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Welcome to Apache test page!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
