<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kernel on The Duck Channel´s Site</title>
    <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/tags/kernel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kernel on The Duck Channel´s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theduckchannel.github.io/tags/kernel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Enable Chaotic-AUR on Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/23/how-to-enable-chaotic-aur-on-arch-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/23/how-to-enable-chaotic-aur-on-arch-linux/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Video Greetings Links Steps  1. Install the Keys 2. Update and Upgrade   Finish  Video   Greetings Hi all, in this video i will show how to enable Chaotic-AUR on Arch Linux.
Chaotic-AUR is a unofficial user reposity for Arch Linux that has prebuilt binaries from the AUR.
Several apps and custom kernels are available in this repo, and this includes kernels specially tuned for gamer and desktop use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install tkg Gamer Kernel to Speed Booster on Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/21/install-tkg-gamer-kernel-to-speed-booster-on-arch-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/21/install-tkg-gamer-kernel-to-speed-booster-on-arch-linux/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Video Greetings Links Steps  1. Chaotic-AUR 2. Enable Chaotic-AUR 3. Install TKG Kernel 4. Customize Grub   Finish  Video   Greetings Hi all, in this video i will show how to install TKG Gamer Kernel on Arch Linux.
You only need have one system with Arch Linux fully installed.
I hope you enjoy!
Links  Arch Linux Arch Linux Wiki Arch Linux Wiki - Kernel Chaotic-AUR  Steps 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux Full Install with bspwm</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/20/arch-linux-full-install-with-bspwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/2021/08/20/arch-linux-full-install-with-bspwm/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, in this video i will show how to full install Arch Linux with bspwm desktop environment.
 The boot mode will be EFI. I’m assuming you already have the usb stick with the Arch Linux ISO. If you use wireless network, please go to the site in the description and see the link to properly configure your network.  I hope you enjoy!
Links  Download the latest Arch Linux ISO Connect to the Internet - Arch Linux Wiki Yay Arch Linux Wiki - Swap File Duck Channel´s bspwm-install  1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Webmin on Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/17082021/install-webmin-on-arch-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/17082021/install-webmin-on-arch-linux/</guid>
      <description>How to Install Webmin on Arch Linux [2021]
Links  Webmin Arch Linux Wiki Yay AUR Helper  0. Intro Hi all, in this video i will show how to install Webmin on Arch Linux.
Webmin is a web-based interface for system administration for Unix. Using any modern web browser, you can setup user accounts, Apache, DNS, file sharing and much more.
I hope you enjoy!
1. Enable AUR If you have AUR enabled in your system, please go to the next section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux Btrfs Kde Plasma Full Install [2021]</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/13082021/arch-linux-btrfs-kde-plasma-full-install-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/13082021/arch-linux-btrfs-kde-plasma-full-install-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, in this video i will show how to full install Arch Linux with BTRFS filesystem.
 The boot mode will be EFI. I’m assuming you already have the usb stick with the Arch Linux ISO. My internet is wired, so if you have wireless network, please go to the website that is in the description of this video and see the link to properly configure your network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux Dual Boot Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/arch-linux-dual-boot-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/arch-linux-dual-boot-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, in this video i will show how to install Arch Linux Dual Boot with Windows 10.
The bootloader utilized is Grub and boot mode is uefi.
The Arch Linux installation will be only the base system with network and bootloader.
I will use virtual machine, but the procedure is the same and it does not affect.
I hope you enjoy!
Bios  Boot the PC and press the manufacturers key to open the BIOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Arch Linux - 2021</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/how-to-install-arch-linux-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/how-to-install-arch-linux-2021/</guid>
      <description>Commands 1. Set the Keyboard Layout $ loadkeys yourKeyboardLayout The default console keymap is US. Available layouts can be listed with:
$ ls /usr/share/kbd/keymaps/**/*.map.gz 2. Config the Best Mirrors $ reflector -c &amp;quot;BR&amp;quot; -f 12 -n 10 -l 12 \ --save /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist --verbose $ pacman -Syy 3. Partitioning the Disk $ fdisk /dev/yourDevice Create the root partition and the swap.
4. Formatting the partitions use mkfs.ext4, mkswap and mkfs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Cinnamon Desktop Environment on Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/how-to-install-cinnamon-desktop-environment-on-arch-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/how-to-install-cinnamon-desktop-environment-on-arch-linux/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Install Virt Manager on Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/how-to-install-virt-manager-on-arch-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theduckchannel.github.io/post/how-to-install-virt-manager-on-arch-linux/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
